# Jeff Lupinski

Digital Designer Denver, Colorado hello@jefflupinski.com +1 303 345 1962 Portfolio <sup>7</sup> LinkedIn <sup>7</sup>

Digital designer focused on interaction design, interface and experience design, and visual design.

Experienced collaborating with teams to design, lead, and craft solutions for brands in every vertical.

#### Selected Experience

### Senior Designer at BASIC / DEPT

### July 2022 - Aug 2024

We design digital products, services, and eCommerce experiences for category leaders. Contributed and led design for various clients such as Google, Ocean Spray, Nike, and Taco Bell.

#### Senior Designer at Handsome

## Aug 2020 - Jul 2022

Handsome, now Raw Materials, is a holistic experience design agency. I led design projects for brands in assorted industries, including 7-Eleven, FedEx, Meta, AMC Television, and more.

### Freelance Independent Designer

#### May 2012 - Aug 2020

Agencies include Instrument, Ueno, Handsome, and Mondo Robot. Clients include Marriott Bonvoy, Salesforce, Epic Games, Chubb, Twitter, Amazon, Liquid Death, Zwift, Specialized Bicycles, and more.

### Senior Designer at Pluralsight

## May 2018 - Mar 2020

GitPrime/Flow provides deep and analytical insights into the efficiency and performance of software development teams. Led design and creative direction in producing, evolving, and implementing company-wide design systems. In 2019, Pluralsight acquired GitPrime.

## Product Designer at MojoTech

### Oct 2014 - Jul 2018

MojoTech is a full-service digital product agency serving big and soon-to-be-big companies. Created end-to-end digital product designs, collaborating with product owners from concept to completion through complex user interface and experience designs.

## Education

# Bachelor of Science, Graphic Design and Digital Media Johnson and Wales University, 2008 – 2012

Graduated with Honors Cum Laude

Skills

Visual Design Interaction Design User Experience Design
User Interface Design Presentation Skills Design Direction

Digital Product and App Design Deck Design User Research

Design Systems & Libraries Rapid Prototyping Responsive Web Design

## Technology

Figma, Sketch, Adobe Creative Cloud, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, Framer, Principle, Webflow, Origami, Keynote, Al Tools, Midjourney, Frame.io, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Version Control